https://privacy.universalmusic.com/CCPA

Home
CCPA
CCPA
Here at Universal Music Group we take your privacy seriously, and we’re dedicated to providing you with the best possible music experience. Across all of our communications – whether that’s social media, advertising, or even email – we want to make sure we’re delivering marketing messages to you from your favorite artists effectively. That way we show up in the right place at the right time.
To do this, we will occasionally need to share some information about you to our partners to ensure that you get personalized updates from the artists you love.
Do you live in California?
Californian’s have certain rights around how companies collect, use, disclose, and share personal information. We want to deliver the best possible experience to you, the fan, while maintaining this level of privacy. To deliver this experience, we use industry-standard advertising business practices that may be considered a “sale” under the California Consumer Privacy Act.
What does that mean though? Here’s how we might “sell” that information:
By allowing advertising networks with whom we partner to place cookies or other tracking technologies through our sites; and
By sharing hashed or pseudonymized identifiers with advertising networks to create audiences for use in online advertising
California residents have the right to request:
Disclosure of personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you;
Deletion of your personal information that we maintain; and
To opt out of the sale of your personal information.
Just a heads up, UMG does not knowingly sell personal information related to children under 16 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian and have questions about our practices regarding childrens data see our privacy policy or contact the UMG Privacy Office.
Know Your Privacy Choices
You’re in the driver’s seat here. There are a variety of privacy choices you can make to suit your preferences. Here at UMG you have two distinct categories of information that you can adjust based on what you’re comfortable with:
Profile Information includes your name, email or physical address, purchase history, and other information that identifies you and you may opt out of the sale of your Profile Information, designate an authorized representative, make a general privacy request, or request additional information by either contacting the UMG Privacy Office or email us at privacy@universalmusic.com.
Cookie Data includes data associated with your interactions with UMG websites, stores, or apps that use identifiers that cannot directly identify you and you may opt out of the sale of Cookie Data use the cookie consent tools available on our sites. Look for a banner, link, and/or button with the text “Cookie Choices.”
UMG may verify requests regarding Profile Information by confirming that you control the email address associated with your personal information. If necessary – and taking into account available technology, security and privacy concerns, and the burden on our business – we reserve the right to take additional steps or require additional information to verify your request.
This is a safe space and we want you to know that you will not receive any discriminatory treatment for exercising your privacy rights.
Phew! Glad we got through all of that. If you’re still scratching your head or have additional questions or concerns, contact the UMG Privacy Office.
Now let the music play!
Home
UMG
Our Labels & Brands
TASK FORCE FOR MEANINGFUL CHANGE
Social Responsibility
Digital Innovation
For UMG Artists
Careers at UMG
Contact Us
News
Featured News
UNIVERSAL MUSIC PUBLISHING GROUP ACQUIRES BOB DYLAN’S ENTIRE CATALOG OF SONGS Dec 07, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP LAUNCHES MERCURY STUDIOS Dec 03, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC UK LAUNCH 0207 DEF JAM LABEL TO CHAMPION BRITISH MUSIC CULTURE WORLDWIDE Nov 25, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP’S FAMILY OF ARTISTS AND LABELS NOMINATED ACROSS NEARLY EVERY GENRE AT THE 63RD ANNUAL GRAMMY AWARDS Nov 25, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC SOUTH AFRICA PARTNERS WITH NATIONAL SCHOOL OF THE ARTS Nov 10, 2020
CAPITOL MUSIC GROUP’S STEVE BARNETT ANNOUNCES RETIREMENT Nov 05, 2020
BRAVADO, UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP’S GLOBAL MERCHANDISING AND BRAND MANAGEMENT DIVISION, PARTNERS WITH ALIBABA’s TMALL GLOBAL Oct 28, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC PUBLISHING GROUP SIGNS KENDRICK LAMAR TO EXCLUSIVE, GLOBAL PUBLISHING AGREEMENT WITH TOP DAWG ENTERTAINMENT Oct 27, 2020
OSCAR® NOMINEE AND GOLDEN GLOBE® AWARD-WINNER TARAJI P. HENSON TO HOST AND PRODUCE ALONGSIDE WONDERY AND UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP’S 'JACKED: THE RISE OF NEW JACK SWING' Oct 15, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP APPOINTS SIMON JEROME NASSER AS MD, UNIVERSAL MUSIC SINGAPORE & HEAD OF LIVE, SOUTHEAST ASIA Oct 13, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC THAILAND AND IAM RECORDS PARTNER TO LAUNCH LYRA Oct 09, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC INDONESIA ANNOUNCES PARTNERSHIP WITH WONDERLAND RECORDS AND SIGNING OF POPULAR INDONESIAN SINGER RENDY PANDUGO Oct 09, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP AND DAKIA U-VENTURES ANNOUNCE UMUSIC HOTELS Oct 09, 2020
NEW CHAPTER FOR MOTOWN RECORDS WITH UK LABEL LAUNCH Sep 14, 2020
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP AND DADDY YANKEE, GLOBAL SUPERSTAR AND REGGAETON ICON, STRIKE MULTIFACETED GLOBAL STRATEGIC PARTNERSHIP Sep 10, 2020
View all news
SIGN UP TO THE NEWSLETTER BELOW, USING YOUR SOCIAL ACCOUNT OR EMAILFacebookTwitterYouTubeSpotifyEmail* email* zip or postal code* choose countrySelect...AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamas (the)BahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivia (Plurinational State of)Bonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean Territory (the)Brunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCabo VerdeCambodiaCameroonCanadaCayman Islands (the)Central African Republic (the)ChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) Islands (the)ColombiaComoros (the)Congo (the Democratic Republic of the)Congo (the)Cook Islands (the)Costa RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican Republic (the)EcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland Islands (the) [Malvinas]Faroe Islands (the)FijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern Territories (the)GabonGambia (the)GeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly See (the)HondurasHong Kong SAR, ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran (Islamic Republic of)IraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (the Democratic People's Republic of)Korea (the Republic of)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic Republic (the)LatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao SAR, ChinaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall Islands (the)MartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia (Federated States of)Moldova (the Republic of)MonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands (the)New CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNiger (the)NigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth MacedoniaNorthern Mariana Islands (the)NorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippines (the)PitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussian Federation (the)RwandaSaint BarthélemySaint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da CunhaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudan (the)SurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab Republic (the)Taiwan (Province of China)TajikistanTanzania, the United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos Islands (the)TuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab Emirates (the)United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland (the)United States Minor Outlying Islands (the)United States of America (the)UruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic of)Viet NamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis and FutunaWestern Sahara*YemenZambiaZimbabwe* Required fieldsThank you for signing up!THANK YOU!Thank you for registering! We have sent a confirmation email to {USEREMAIL}. Click the link to confirm your email address.Please check your spam folder for the email, if it does not arrive, click this link...resend verification emailCancel
Privacy Policy |
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy |
Terms & Conditions
